http://www.autoalliance.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Alliance of Automobile Manufacturers
Press enter to submit your search
Your SearchesPopularEconomyautonomousmanufacturingawarenesscars moveFeatured How many auto jobs are in your state?
See how autos are transforming our ports
Member Login Auto Alliance - Driving Innovation SearchEconomyInnovationSafetyConnected CarsEnergy & Environment More
NewsAbout the AllianceResource CenterIn Your StateContact Member LoginSearchEconomyInnovationSafetyConnected CarsEnergy & EnvironmentNewsAbout the AllianceResource CenterIn Your StateContact Stay informed with future updates
SubmitPrivacy PolicyThe Alliance of Automobile Manufacturers (“Auto Alliance”) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of visitors to our website. Outlined below is our online privacy policy for information collected through our website and email lists. If you have questions about these policies, we encourage you to email info@autoalliance.actualsize.me.Resale or disclosure of information to third parties: We do not share or otherwise disclose any personal information, including your name, address, or e-mail addresses with other organizations. Only Auto Alliance staff and our authorized agents have access to personally identifiable information provided by visitors to our site.Browser information collected on our website: As with any website operator, the Auto Alliance analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of our website. We use an external service to provide real-time reporting to us and our authorized agents of browser accesses to our site. This reporting includes page views, unique views, unique visitors, repeat visitors, frequency of visits, and peak-volume traffic periods. We do not use this service to gather, request, record, require, collect or track any Internet users’ personally identifiable information.Personalization of Content: We use cookies on our site to personalize the experience of our visitors and to support some necessary functions. We also use cookies to better understand how our visitors use our site.You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies.However, please note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at this and on other sites throughout the Internet may not be complete. In addition, if you do not allow cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by other Internet sites or by us.Privacy of our e-mail lists: The Auto Alliance maintains several email lists to keep supporters, the press and policy makers informed about news and events. Individuals must request to join our mailing lists. Individuals who provide optional information may also receive materials in the U.S. mail and/or be contacted by telephone by authorized Auto Alliance representatives. In addition, we do not share the email addresses on our lists with staff outside of the Auto Alliance and its authorized agents. We configure our list server software to refuse to divulge the email addresses of our list subscribers to anyone but authorized Auto Alliance staff and agents. Only Auto Alliance staff and our authorized agents have access to personally identifiable information provided by visitors to our site.Children’s privacy: Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulation establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. Our site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13, and we have designed our site to block our knowing acceptance of information from children under 13 whenever age-related information is requested.It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the notification, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of information by children under 13, please do so by emailing us at: info@autoalliance.actualsize.me.Security: We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving financial data from our site. In addition, we have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss or misuse of information at our site that we have collected from you. NewsAbout the AllianceResource CenterIn Your StateContact
Privacy Policy © Alliance of Automobile Manufacturers
Signup Fuel Economy &Carbon ReductionsAccording to consumer research, our customers want it all — better mileage, cleaner and safer technologies and affordable new vehicles. While we continue urging all stakeholders to work together toward a national program for fuel economy standards, automakers have our own roadmap to move forward while continuing to meet the needs and expectations of consumers. Our priorities are fourfoldContinue increasing fuel economy — year after year — to provide our customers with more energy-efficient vehicles with greater emissions reductions and the latest safety technologies.Partner with public/private groups to get more energy-efficient vehicles on our roads via charging/fueling infrastructure, consumer incentives, government fleet sales and car-sharing and ride-sharing programs.At the same time, continue increasing investments in research & development for more advancements in safety and efficiency.Do all of this while still keeping new vehicles affordable.OUR ROADMAP FOR
